Carl Sachs

Full-Stack Developer

sachscarl@gmail.com | (313) 330-7308 | | Detroit, MI 48225

carlsachs.com | twitter.com/CarltonSachs | in/carl-sachs/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a motivated and hard-working individual with a knack for juggling projects in a timely and efficient manner. I pick up on concepts quickly, and love to expand my knowledge learning by experience. I am open to both remote and on-site opportunities, and would love to focus in React.js and have a natural lack for design.

WORK HISTORY

Lambda X. Remote

Student | 09/2020 - Current

- I am currently looking for opportunities and working with Lambda X
- Planned, prepared and participated in weekly meetings and events
- Reported back to instructor and management to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities

Andiamo Detroit Riverfront. Detroit, Michigan *Bartender/Server* | 01/2018 - 06/2019

- Collaborated with kitchen team to support order preparation, manage efficient deliveries and minimize customer service issues by verifying meals
- Upsold high-profit items such as appetizers and mixed drinks to increase sales and profits
- Worked with POS system to place orders, manage bills and handle complimentary items
- Enhanced operational efficiency by using slow periods to restock supplies

Coach Insignia. Detroit, Michigan Server | 12/2016 - 05/2017

SKILLS

- React
- CSS
- HTML5
- Node.js
- Bootstrap
- Python
- Team Collaboration
- Slack
- TailwindCSS
- Publish NPM Libraries
- Expo
- React-Native
- Styled-Components
- Javascript
- Pair Programming
- Trello

EDUCATION

Lambda School

Remote 09/2020

Lambda School Endorsement, Full-Stack Web Development: Full-Stack Development I took Lambda's Full-Stack Web Development course, completed

Sep 1st, 2020.

- Created a high-end experience for clientele.
- My main takeaway was that the small details are what matter most.
- Upsold high-profit items such as appetizers and mixed drinks to increase sales and profits
- Created orders, documented special requests and followed up with kitchen personnel to foster top-quality service

PROJECTS

Find my Github Profile Here: https://github.com/carlsachs Find my Projects here: https://carlsachs.com/projects

Skills:

- React, Node, HTML, CSS, Knex, Python, Javascript, and more
- Team Collaboration, Pair Programming, Direct Reporting, and more

Wayne State University
Detroit
2019

Business Finance Coursework in Entrepreneurship, Finance, and Business Admin.

• Avg. 3.6 GPA